const questions = [
  { question: "　結（link）", answer: "連", choices: ["連","運","諢","逢"] },
  { question: "　步（step back）", answer: "卻", choices: ["卻","欲","浴","谷"] },
  { question: "　易（easy）", answer: "容", choices: ["容","客","害","官"] },
  { question: "應　（should）", answer: "該", choices: ["該","旋","認","誌"] },
  { question: "辯　（debate）", answer: "論", choices: ["論","請","講","調"] },
  { question: "規　（rule）", answer: "則", choices: ["則","側","剛","刪"] },
  { question: "家　（housework）", answer: "務", choices: ["務","霧","防","勉"] },
  { question: "　本（basic）", answer: "基", choices: ["基","甚","機","箕"] },
  { question: "　定（decide）", answer: "決", choices: ["決","快","缺","块"] },
  { question: "　文（gentle）", answer: "斯", choices: ["斯","欺","散","鄭"] },
  { question: "　齊（tidy）", answer: "整", choices: ["整","正","極","歪"] },
  { question: "　到（reach）", answer: "達", choices: ["達","運","連","逢"] }
];
